{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Solar Water Heater Installers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40358/":{"taskOID":40358,"originalTaskOID":40358,"setID":652,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4152,"questionDisplayText":"Size of Heater","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you know what size water heater you need?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":465,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"30 gallon","answerDisplayText":"30 gallon","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":525,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"50 gallon","answerDisplayText":"50 gallon","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":494,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"40 gallon","answerDisplayText":"40 gallon","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8117,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6896,"questionDisplayText":"Heat spa or pool","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Will this solar water heater be used to heat a spa or pool?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9816,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1580,"questionDisplayText":"Location of water heater","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where is the water heater located?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":958,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Basement","answerDisplayText":"Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1712,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Crawl space","answerDisplayText":"Crawl space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1450,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Closet","answerDisplayText":"Closet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":881,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Attic","answerDisplayText":"Attic","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6179,"questionDisplayText":"Installation location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is your chosen installation location:","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7980,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Shaded at any time during the year","answerDisplayText":"Shaded at any time during the year","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7981,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Southern or Western facing","answerDisplayText":"Southern or Western facing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4152,"questionDisplayText":"Size of Heater","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you know what size water heater you need?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":465,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"30 gallon","answerDisplayText":"30 gallon","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":525,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"50 gallon","answerDisplayText":"50 gallon","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":494,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"40 gallon","answerDisplayText":"40 gallon","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8117,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":465,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"30 gallon","answerDisplayText":"30 gallon","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":525,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"50 gallon","answerDisplayText":"50 gallon","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":494,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"40 gallon","answerDisplayText":"40 gallon","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8117,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6896,"questionDisplayText":"Heat spa or pool","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Will this solar water heater be used to heat a spa or pool?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9816,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9816,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1580,"questionDisplayText":"Location of water heater","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where is the water heater located?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":958,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Basement","answerDisplayText":"Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1712,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Crawl space","answerDisplayText":"Crawl space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1450,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Closet","answerDisplayText":"Closet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":881,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Attic","answerDisplayText":"Attic","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":958,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Basement","answerDisplayText":"Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1712,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Crawl space","answerDisplayText":"Crawl space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1450,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Closet","answerDisplayText":"Closet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":881,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Attic","answerDisplayText":"Attic","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6179,"questionDisplayText":"Installation location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is your chosen installation location:","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7980,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Shaded at any time during the year","answerDisplayText":"Shaded at any time during the year","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7981,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Southern or Western facing","answerDisplayText":"Southern or Western facing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":7980,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Shaded at any time during the year","answerDisplayText":"Shaded at any time during the year","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7981,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Southern or Western facing","answerDisplayText":"Southern or Western facing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40358/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40358,"taskName":"Solar Water Heater System - Install","taskDescription":"Install a Solar Water Heater System","xmTaskDescriptor":"Solar Water Heater Installers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":368,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Solar Heater Water system thermosiphon","textMessagingName":"Inst Solar Wtr Htr","rolloverLongDesc":"Done by solar specialists. Heating systems collect solar energy \u0026 use it to heat a fluid which is then circulated throughout the building.","rolloverShortDesc":"Solar hot water systems.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install a Solar Water Heater System. HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened solar water heating installation contractors in your area.","htmlTitle":"Solar Water Heater Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Replace or Install New","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":102,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":3,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Solar Water Heater System Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Solar Water Heater System - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Solar Water Heating Project","urlName":"Solar-Water-Heater-Install-or-Replace","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Solar Water Heater Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Solar,Heater,Water,system,thermosiphon,indirect","emcCategoryOid":-14820,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":652,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}